Nighttime and Idol
My Three Major Predictions
This is a section where you will be introduced to the three elements that make up this earthquake.
The idea is to get to know your idols better!
Now, what are the three elements that make up Mr. Date?
Here we go!
Yes!
Ready!
Ta-da!
Three elements for me.
Yes, the first one.
Money!
Number one, money!
Number two.
Meat and white rice!
Meat and rice?
Three.
Music!
Music on three!
Yes, now we have paper.
Paper is made of paper?
I see. God.
Yes, God.
Well, that's not so easy, but it has a meaning, doesn't it?
First of all, it means money.
Money.
Money is a difficult thing to mention when you are an idol.
Is that so?
No, that's not it.
Of course not.
People don't put money into idols at night.
No, they don't.
Why is that?
Let's dig a little deeper.
Yes.
It's not right.
Yes, it is strange.
Yes, it is. That much.
Money is important, isn't it?
Even if you have to live and live on it.
Of course.
Idols.
Even for animated films.
That's right.
Yes.
Money.
No, yes.
No, it's a little bit inflated.
I see. But, you know, recently, prices of things have been going up.
Yes, that's right. Prices are going up, and taxes are going up, too.
Yes, yes.
No, I would like to tell that to the government.
I want to tell that to the government.
I want the tax rate to be lowered a little more.
You are going to step in today, aren't you? It's all right.
I'll go out with you for the rest of the night. I'll go out with you for the rest of the night.
What?
Say "motivation.
Motivation.
Complain about the government.
I'm not complaining about taxes.
Motivation.
Money is my motivation.
No, there are typical manipulative idols like this in the world.
Isn't that the ideal idol image?
Money is not.
It's amazing.
I think it's an association game.
I'm signing up.
I knew it.
I saw it.
I'm learning a lot from you.
Night, you're in trouble.
I'm in trouble, aren't I? This exchange.
But I like it.
I think this is something you should participate in.
Really?
But you want to be up there while you're still alive.
What do you think? I was thrown that idea.
I was thrown that theme.
You have to interpret it. Your job is to speak from here.
Let's see how you interpret the captain's thoughts.
I understand.
Thank you very much.
What do you want me to do?
What do you want me to do with a round of money?
Money is very important. Hobbies.
I have a lot of hobbies.
I go fishing.
I buy clothes, so I can't do anything without money.
Well, that's true.
That's why I need money.
But, you know, I'm a professional, so I can't do anything without it.
I'm a professional, so I value it as compensation.
That's important, isn't it?
That's important.
There are too many difficult words.
You know, difficult words...
Consideration.
Compensation.Consideration
Well, it's certainly a consideration, but it's also... you know... you know...
Because of what I've done.
I'm evaluating people.
Of course, there are things like cheering, but...
Why are you following them?
After all...
You're your own celebrity, right?
No, I don't.
But I love her.
I understand.
Yes, I do.
Please, by all means.
Please buy Tomo's commercial!
Please buy her picture!
Thank you very much.
Beef tongue served at a beef tongue restaurant is different, isn't it?
It's different, it's different!
I really want you to enjoy the difference!
It's like it's only for the patient.
Why?
I'm just trying to enjoy it.
This show is...
Harupyon
Hi, you're back!
See you later.
Coco Chanmaru
Zundare-san
Sent to you courtesy of Ms. Nogi from Taiwan!
Thank you, everyone!
Thank you!